Guide to the George Mason University photograph collection, 1950s-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: University Relations, 1950s-1999; (37 boxes)
  - Gloriana singers at Richmond, May 01, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Mary Ishee, Keike and Ron at computer, Anthropology faculty, May 02, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Share the Earth conference, Forensics team, Zonta scholarship donation, May 03, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Jane Flynn, May 04, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Carolyn Kurylo at West Springfield High School, May 06, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Student awards, Pat Caretta, May 09, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Composers and conductors, Kurzweil machine, Library automation, May 10, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Graduation, Frank Spindler, Board of Visitors, May 21, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Katt Scholarship, SUB II conference (Tombes), Kravitz, Hanging student art, May 25, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Arts explosion, Writers, Artists, video, Theatre, Stillman conference, June 10, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Eugene Donelly, Check donation (H.A.), June 20, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Terry Cochran, Student art, June 20, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Buildings, students, P.A.G.E. meeting, New Presidents house, June 23, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Books by English faculty, teleconference, June 28, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Glenn Smith and Diane Peltz, check present, students on lawn, July 07, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Minority student registration, Arena contract signing, July 11, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Computer center, students posed in front of dorms, July 12, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Fairfax festival (HA), ORF Technique class (ML), July 15, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Mike Kelley, Basketball clinic, July 23, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Joan Fisher and Development staff, STP lunch, July 28, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Lou Wetherbee, Wolftrap, Tyson's, Vernon Grad and Jo Pacheco, GMU, Korean book donation, August 09, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Modular buildings, Patriot circle construction, field house, Arena (architect's original drawing), original campus (copy), August 11, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Computer center, library automation, Wade Gilley, Cheerleaders, Registration, computer installation, August 17, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Student services directors, library, construction, M.T. at Torpedo factory, August 18, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Market processes orient, 1st page lecture, campus scenes, Dance Kodalith, August 28, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sheeba Sharrow, P.A.G.E. reception, campus scenes, September 02, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Men's soccer, campus scenes, September 06, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Portraits-Tom Deitz, J.B. Blunk, Bob Crouch, Richard Barton, Henry Lampe, September 07, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Gerry Hill and Chuck Render, Budget meeting, campus scenes, September 09, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - G. Johnson, Walter Williams, campus, September 21, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Patriot's day, September 23, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Artist's proposal models, September 29, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Hewlett Packard donations to P.A.G.E., GMU press at Gunston Hall, October 01, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Management faculty, Nancy Joyner and Carol Thudium, campus, October 05, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - University Police staff, glass of beer, October 06, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - University Police staff, Budget cut meeting, Kravitz installation, October 07, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - "Ms. Page" Robot, Misc. copies for arts explosion, October 11, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Pat Roberson, Scott Whitney, Canadian emblem, Law school library, October 12, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Faculty showcase, Philips collection, Town and Gown tea, October 15, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Biology department, Arthur Peterson, Law school, new offices In library tower, October 17, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Doug Mose in TV studio, Art in Ac.III, October 19, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Gordon Tullock, Arts explosion copies, October 25, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Arts and Gala auction, October 29, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Campus, biology, Field trips (on campus), October 31, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Campus, Fairfax city, scholarly journals, November 03, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - TV studio, Men's soccer, November 04, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Campus scenes, Philips collection, November 08, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Library of Congress, Capitol, Kennedy center, campus, "Gin game", November 09, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Campus, scenes Brecht on Brecht, November 11, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Jonas, Kelso, Jones, Riordan, Biology lab, student apartments, November 14, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Center for study of Young Children, November 16, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Riordan/Hutchinson, Bausch, Clemmer/Kimble, Gloriana Singers, African fashions, November 17, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Defur, Siff, kid with computer, November 21, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Christmas chorus, campus, November 23, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Goodwin, Galler, Mathy House communications, Kravitz and Kendall, Frazier and Gotkin at WEEL, SUB II, December 01, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Hyack, Burton, Dahlin and Copeland, dance rehersal, Robb press conference, December 02, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Minority students reception, Rev. Baltimore, "No Problem" in RAT, December 04, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Chesapeake Bay conference, H-P Calculator gift, December 07, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Glenn Smith, December 09, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Campus scenes, June 06, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Campus scenes, lecture, June 06, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Ralph Barocas-Psychology, June 06, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - John Allen-Psychology, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Peter Black-Sociology and Anthropology, 1984-1997 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Debate team, GMI luncheon, January 03, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - D. King, GMI Donation, development art donation, January 05, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - S. Looney, J. Allen, Public affairs staff, Mathy House communications, January 10, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - A. Hickey, K. Wiley, J. Leuy, L. Bowen, office move, Herrity/H.E.P., January 16, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - M. Black, E. Norris, J. Greenberg, January 18, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - GMI Portrait copies, Virginia General Assembly, January 20, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Admissions counselors, E. Doyle, Johnson at Faculty Senate, January 24, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - A. Peterson, A. Haley, M. Berry, Cit press conference, January 30, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - G.Johnson, B. Dahlin, Shen C.Y. Fu, February 06, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Dance class, February 08, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - A. Haley, M. Berry, Satellite dish, Dancers feet for poster, February 10, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Counseling center, February 13, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - D. Rothbart, Faculty senate meeting, M.Black with student assistant, February 15, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Circuit board close-ups, February 24, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Liu and Burke, Roth, Cozzins and Caulder, Milor, February 28, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - J. Allen, Faculty books, International studies, March 06, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - A. Taylor, D. Bushnell, S. Folliet, J. Simecca, J. Cohn, March 08, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Circuit boards, Kodalith copies, March 09, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Kodalith circuit boards, March 16, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - H. Feinstein, Library, campus, March 20, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Barocas, Haddad, D. Foster, Special collections and Archives staff, J. Fletcher, B. Peters, March 24, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Faculty senate officers, Bill Lankford, computer hardware, campus, March 26, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - S. Seeberg, Claudia Murphy, Public affairs, DandP staffs (for M.T.), March 28, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Campus, wiring Finley, student forum, Robinson computer center, March 30, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Campus scenes, Liu and nursing students in TV studio, April 03, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Palmeri and Cassara, Shannon Jordan, PAGE lounge, student editors, April 05, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Shannon Jordan, Service award breakfast, University day, Mobil donation, April 10, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Johnson/Mobil's donation, campus, April 13, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Center for Public choice staff, General campus, student close-ups, April 17, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Law library, Steve Burnette, Center Market Proc. Group, Bill Lankford, April 20, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Mason Day, April 27, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Pediatric nursing student at Fairfax Hospital, Secretary's lunch day, April 30, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Counseling center, E. Sibley, David Brickley, Gary Axelson, May 02, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Student awards, Forensic team, Diane Miller, May 04, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Dick Bausch, John McCarty, campus scenes, May 07, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Market processes reception, May 11, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - S. Daughty, Jo Pacheco, Joe D'Agostino with Betsy Dahlin, PhD/conflict resolution graduates, May 15, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Graduation 1984, May 19, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Bill Cohn, Chris Thaiss, Biology field trip (water sampling), May 22, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Aiko Miller reception, Taiwan art show opening (Green Springs), June 07, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - B. Clark, A. Furgeson, R. Carty, Mr.and Mrs. Lampe with Joel Brayhill, June 13, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Joe D'Agostino, STP orientation, Arena construction, campus, June 15, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Dace Schaefer, Alan Srebnick, campus, library, June 15, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Brian Turner, campus scenes, June 25, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - STP students, Evelyn Moore, Telecommunications staff, July 02, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Westgate fellowship, Durch. Mgmt. scholarship, campus, July 11, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Alumni move, David Arrow, Korean deans, Joe O'Hare, July 16, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Portraits (B. Render, M. Deshmukh, S. Saperstone, J. Flinn P. Black, J. English), July 20, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - STP students for hometown releases, Fenwick Library at night, July 23, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Psychology heads with J. Allen, General campus, law scholarships, July 25, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Patrice Alverado, Psychology testing, Gala quilting, general campus, Marilyn, Guiffre, July 26, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Lee Swann, Angie Barnes, Law school computer center, August 01, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Michelle LeSane, Korean visitors with Johnson, August 07, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Module and Arena construction, Suz rear, Kravitz sculpture in suz, August 15, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Portraits (Alan Srebnick, Jim Lewis, Joanne Johnson, Charlene Hurt), August 22, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - New students picnic, Real estate association, library scholarships, August 24, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Rojer Lewis, Louis Meites, student groups around campus, August 28, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Peter Klappert copy, student groups around campus, August 29, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - campus scenes, "Midsummer Night's Dream" promo shots, September 04, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - campus scenes, library interiors, module erection, September 06, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - corporate art show promo (at ATandT), H. Floyd, students studying, September 12, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Art book donation, Suz road, portraits (Elizabeth Walker, Helen Hill Miller, Hector Alcalde), September 14, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Students around campus, field house, Patriot Village trailers, September 18, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Biology boat on Pohick, Arena construction, casual campus shots, September 19, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - R. Draper, Patriot's Day (close-us and student groups), September 21, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Dance student (Nancy) in "running" pose, GMI meeting, September 24, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Portraits (M. Kafatos, G. Johnson, F. Matthews, K. Davies, S. Ruth), September 27, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Biology boat on Pohick Bay, Arena construction, students through woods, October 02, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - S. Campbell computer class, Mash with students, Black Hole Conference, October 08, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - R. Kerns with African art donation, dance concert rehersal, October 12, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Rear of Roberts Rd. House, Portraits (O. Wahl, D'Agostino, Carlos Yates), October 15, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Psychology clinic staff, D. Bausch, V. Gras, Ricky Wilson, October 18, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Athletic sponsors, African art donors, J. Cohn, Christakis/Keever, October 22, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Johnson with students, Arena crane accident documentation, October 29, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - South American conference, Riordan with students, Sperry Don, Quilt, Dog, November 08, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Biology faculty, Brazilian rectors, V. Gras, F. Singer, November 15, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Artmobile interiors, GMU chorale, student murals, November 16, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - New electron microscope, Portraits (R. Clark, M. Emsley, M. Behrman), November 29, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Arts Gala, December 06, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Crafts fair, Portraits (G. Smith, L. Miller, D. Boehm-Davis) Relay board, December 12, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - David Bever-Fire Fighter, June 07, 1905 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - John Burton-ICAR, June 07, 1905 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Susan Campbell-Computer and Information systems, June 07, 1905 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Stephen Burton-Performing Arts, Music, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - George W. Johnson and Joanne Johnson, 1985-1989 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Deborah Boehm-Davis-Provost's office, 1985-1994 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Kevin Avruch-Sociology and Anthropology, 1985-1996 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Benjamin Broome-Communications, 1985-1997 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Mike Behrman-Special Education, 1985-1997 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Chester Neudling, GMI lunch with Virginia Education Department representatives, January 09, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - K. Hoffman, W. Giley and M. Crain, A. Tombes, Reinhart Award winners, January 12, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - L. Hecht, S. Burton, classroom cafeteria, Peterson copy, January 18, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - F. Matthews, C. Thomas, S. Burton, Kravitz sculpture, GMI donation, January 21, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - J. Flecher, Biology lab class, January 24, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - D. Bushnell with technician group, P. Thomas, sculpture, library, January 30, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Volleyball (vs. UCLA), art class, show scenes George's Hall, February 01, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - J. Foreman, E. Damich, J. High V. Vanberg, R. Fink, D. Lavoie, February 08, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - R. Erlich, M. Crain with assistant, D. Thornhill, studio production class, February 12, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Market processes seminar, Dance rehersals and setups, February 15, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - R. Carty, M. Silva, Peterson play-poetry for children, February 19, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - D. Thornhill, J. Polivka, Reinaldo Lopez, William Gazale, February 25, 2985 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Portraits (E. Joyce, J. Costello, Shirley Chisolm, Renee Poussant), February 28, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Portraits, Punk band in Rat, March 5-12, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Unloading stone for Lopez sculpture, March 15, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - M. Berhman, R. Smith, J. Allen, A. Tombes, K. Smith, F. Grossberg, March 20, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Mielczarek, M. Crain, M. Rice, S. Ruth, P. Dawson, L. Law Jones and Mulvey, March 22, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - M. Spikell, Dance concert rehersal, March 25, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Lopez sculpting, T. Johnson, B. Warner, student play promo, March 27, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Portraits (M. Kelley, T. Johnson, B. Warner), March 29, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Lopez sculpting, Dance class, April 01, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Video class, Dance concert rehersal, exercise class, volleyball practice, April 03, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Co-ops, Lopez sculpting, conflict management, D. Halstead, A. Golcoechea, April 04, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - University day, chain Potok, English and Heenan, Tullock and Buchanan, April 08, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Portraits (C. Mattusch, S. Slayden, S. Goodwin, P. Duara, J. D'Amico), April 10, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Women's track team practice, April 15, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - East Carolina South Championship Men's meet, Denise Fleener, Rob Musio, April 18, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - D. Fleenor, C. Calder, Arena, Social welfare faculty, campus, war play, April 23, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Gilley and Fluner, Lorraine Brown, Outdoor class, campus, April 26, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Lopez sculpture, Portraits (Pfiffner, Cassara, Columb, Lawry, Radner, Doworzecka), May 01, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Kimmel, Censer, "Human Sculpture", Games for physically Handicapped, Library interior, May 06, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Michelle Lesane, Candance Hill, General campus, May 08, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - A. Soll, R. Perry, E. Hendrix, Lopez sculpture, campus, May 10, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Washington Dc attractions, Daniel Rothbart, May 13, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Capital outlay, Governor Robb, Holsinger, Christakis, Westgate school, May 16, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Portraits (Jones, Krech, Stein, Schack, Reithlingschoefer, Lopez, Hemlock Overlook), May 30, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Abdi Bile Abdi, Ihrahim Okash, Fenwick gallery, campus, June 04, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Ann Palkovich, M. Johnson, Colchester archeology dig, June 07, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Portraits (D. Mash, Ron Shayka, J. Smith, C. Hertnecky), June 12, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Camp Mason staff, campus fix-up, Lopez sculpture, General campus, June 14, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - STP Open House, Campus fix-up operations, General campus, June 20, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - L. Liggio, F. Matthews, General campus, Roberts Rd. house, circuit board, June 24, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Portraits (21 people), July 09, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Margaret Brinig-Law School, July 19, 1985-August 20, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - D. Mose on geology set, D. Schaefer in lab, Jerry Capsaddle, July 24, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Portraits (7 people), August 07, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Kathleen Katz, computer with hand closeup, Quarante single cover, August 12, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - R. Rosenwieg, Ladies with arts gala auction car, August 14, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Portraits (12 people), August 19, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Magazine copies, Quilt close-ups, Faculty books, August 24, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Super computer press conference, Humanities construction, General campus, August 28, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Saul Bakash, Students in library, general campus, September 02, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - G. Handleman, J. Riskland, Patriot center construction, September 05, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - J. Levy, H.H. Miller, career services andcounseling staff, campus, September 10, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - D. Mash and G. Handleman, Patriot center, Physical education HDCP instruction class, September 12, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Patriot center press conference, general campus PREL office renovation, September 16, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Hemlook overlook and staff, confidence training course, September 18, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - George Benson concert, crew club demo in quad, September 19, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Patriot's day, General campus, September 20, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Portraits (3 people), September 20, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - "Scapino" promotion, Gloriana singers, Draft posters, brickwork, September 24, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - George Johnson in his office, Haw school students, Marvis Harris, September 27, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Transportation leadership workshop, September 30, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Bullets/Knicks game, new dorm dedication, October 02, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - J. Buie, D. Bafundo, mail room staff at work, October 04, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Portraits (7 people), October 07, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Peter Brunette-English, October 9, 1985-January 25, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Portraits (11 people), Board of visitors, October 09, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Rei Berroa-Foreign Language and Literature, October 11, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Portraits (12 people), October 14, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Marjorie Brown-Azarowicz-Education, January 00, 1900 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - United Way promo, "As You Like It" promo, students, general campus, October 18, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Portraits (15), October 24, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Gunston Hall, Portraits (3), G. Johnson donation, October 28, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - FTP copies, Ezra pound and Dance group copies, October 30, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Symphonic Winds, Spyro gyra and dance concerts, October 31, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Portraits (10), November 04, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - G. Johnson at home, GMU vs. Marathon Oil (basketball) Patriot center, November 04, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Ruth Kaplan Student recruitment fair, November 08, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Portraits (3), November 11, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Fall dance concert promo, pill bottle setup, November 15, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Arts Gala ball and auction, November 16, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Housekeeping services staff at work, November 18, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Tskui, Nursing students, Library computer, maps, November 20, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Portraits (5), November 22, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Brack Brown group, Chataqua book donation, V. West retirement, December 04, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Jesse Jackson in SBU II, GMU vs. Georgetown, December 06, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Christmas Fanfare, Faculty art show, student club, campus, December 09, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Portraits (14), December 11, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Kenneth Bumgarner-Associate Dean of Student Life, June 08, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Dr. James Buchanan Nobel Prize Ceremony and Reception, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Laura Adamkewicz-Associate professor Biology, 1986-1994 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Marta Renzi with Dance Company, B.H.M. Jody Powell, O'Leary copies, January 08, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Portraits (6), January 10, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Helen Hill Miller at Gunston Hall and home, "Power of No" play, January 21, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - M.L.K. Jr. Holiday celebrations, "Annie" setup, C. Raphael, January 23, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Portraits (Vaughn, Kovach, Cody, Roback, McMenamin, R. Bausch, Ch. Smith/exercise), January 24, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - "Luan Hampton Laverty Oberlander" promo, H.H. Miller books, January 28, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Tom Filion in Philadelphia, January 30, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - GMU vs. USC volleyball, Snow scenes, Center for Study of Young Children, February 03, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Alumni relations, Portraits (Bowen, Harrison, Torzilli, Hart, E. Doyle, Defur, Sears), February 05, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Nikki Givoanni, PAGE students in H.T., February 07, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Bradley and Leung, Project for study of Young Children, Campus, newsbox, February 11, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Employee exercise class, February 13, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Nurse group, HB, Portraits (Kafatos, Mose, Siff, Molin, L. White, Erlich, Early), February 17, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)